饥饿
的青春
第二季  第十二集
0,0,0,fx,学习
0,0,0,fx,分享
0,0,0,fx,进步
本字幕由ZiMuZu原创翻译
最新下载请登录www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻译   冰蓝     妖精希亚
翻译  啾啾     roaddog
校对  roaddog
时间轴 JimmyBeck
后期 斯人       总监 roaddog
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    ustvboom
了解最新影视字幕发布信息
我的星期内裤收进来了
Okay, my "Days of the week" undies are done,
但你的胸罩还在外面晾着
but your bra is still out there drying.
还没干吗  面积也不大啊
Still? There's not much there to dry.
这又不好笑
It's not funny.
等等  周五的内裤呢
Hey, wait, where's Friday?
不  今天是周六
No, today's Saturday.
你好  谢天谢地是周五
Hello. Ho-oh! Thank god it's Friday.
它落到我的车上了
Yeah, they fell on my car.
其实这条内裤还去过
You know, that's actually not the craziest place
更怪的地方呢
that pair has landed.
我想听听更多细节  我是泰勒
I'd like to hear more about that. I'm Tyler.
-我是加比  -我是索菲亚
- I'm Gabi. - I'm Sofia.
她有男友  我没有
She has a boyfriend. I do not.
我也没有...男友
Neither do I... have a boyfriend.
在旧金山得说明  特别是顶着这发型
You have to say that in San Francisco. Especially with this hair.
真的很帅
It's really pretty.
既然我已经见过你的内裤了
Well, since I've already seen your underwear,
我觉得我请你吃晚餐才合适
I think it's only right that I buy you dinner.
好啊
Oh. Yeah.
我是说  不行  等等
I mean, no. Wait!
也许可以吧  有点复杂
Maybe. It's kind of complicated.
等等  我弄糊涂了
Wait, I'm confused.
你真有男朋友吗
Wait, so you do have a boyfriend?
不  我有个老板
No, I have a boss.
你知道的  当你有对象而老板没有时
And you know how when you're dating someone and your boss isn't,
-会有些尴尬  -不会啊
- it can be kind of awkward? - Not really.
能让我们单独聊会儿吗
Can you excuse us for a minute, please?
-我其实...  -待在这里  给
- I kind of have-- - Stay here. Here.
松饼啊
Ooh, a muffin.
加比  你为什么想着乔什
Gabi, why are you thinking about Josh?
你的内内飘向了那个帅哥  相信它的智慧
Your panties flew to that guy. Trust their wisdom.
我知道  但我刚回乔什家工作
Yeah, I know, but I just started going back to work at Josh's,
我怕我俩的关系很脆弱
and I'm afraid it's just so delicate
如果我开始跟别人约会  我俩之间就会很奇怪
that if I start dating someone, it could be kinda weird.
那就别在上班时说这事
Yeah, well, then just don't talk about it at work.
我还真没想过
That had never occurred to me.
泰勒  我很乐意跟你约会
Uh, Tyler, hi. I'd love to go out with you.
什么时候
When?
-你最喜欢什么颜色  -黑色
- What's your favorite color? - Black.
那就周三吧
Wednesday it is.
加比  你今早好安静啊
Gabi, you're awfully quiet this morning.
因为我忙着不说那件事
That's because I'm too busy not talking about it.
-什么事  -我碰上了一个大帅哥
- Not talking about what? - I met the cutest guy!
他出现在我家门口
He showed up right at my door
寻找我内裤的主人
looking for the owner of my underwear.
简直像是童话一样
It's like a fairy tale.
早上好
Good morning.
你最爱的教母出现了
Here comes your favorite godmother.
那你就是丑陋的继姐姐吗
Which makes you what, the ugly stepsister?
多说点这帅哥的情况啊
So tell me more about this guy.
好  他玩乐队  是耍棍子的
Okay. He's in a band, and he plays the sticks.
也就是说他是打鼓的
Which means he plays the drums.
打鼓的男人好性感啊
It is so sexy when some guy just plays the--
你走进来  加比就闭嘴了
Wow! When you walk in, Gabi shuts up.
你怎么做到的  教教我吧
How did you do that? Teach me!
很容易
Well, it's easy.
你只用在她说男人时走进来
All you do is catch her when she's talking about a guy.
我才没说什么男人呢
I was not talking about a guy.
我说的是《布偶大电影》里的动物
I was talking about animal from The Muppets.
对  他打鼓
Yeah. He plays the drums.
尤兰达以为他弹吉他  所以...
Yolanda thought he played the guitar, which is why--
加比
Gabi.
你可以聊你的约会
It's okay to talk about your dating life.
真的吗  你不觉得奇怪吗
Really? It doesn't make you feel weird?
你不难受吗  你这样说不是为了
You're not uncomfortable? You're not just saying that
装坚强  因为你心如死灰吗
to put on a brave face 'cause secretly you're dying inside?
加比  我跟你保证
Gabi, I promise you.
我完全没意见
I'm totally cool with it.
他特别有意见
He's so not cool with it.
加比  我以为我们说好了上班不提这事
Gabi, I thought we talked about you not talking about it at work.
没错  我没做到
We did. And I failed.
但好消息是  我意识到我只用撮合乔什
But the good news is I realized all I have to do is set up Josh.
坏消息是  那是最蠢的主意
And the bad news is that's the dumbest idea ever.
不  索菲亚  他不会接受我跟泰勒约会的
No. Sofia, he's not gonna be cool with me dating Tyler
除非他也跟别人约会  你怎么会不懂这个
Unless he's dating somebody too. How do you not know this?
也许因为我脑子里都是知识
Well, because my brain runs on knowledge,
而不是洋葱圈渣
not funyun dust.
你觉得乔什会喜欢你那个漂亮朋友迪迪吗
Hey, do you think josh would be into your pretty friend Dee Dee?
性病迪迪吗
ST-Dee-Dee?
我觉得不会
I don't think so.
那个谁呢  不行
Oh, what about... no.
那个谁呢  算了
Hey, what about... no.
那么...
What about...
她呢
her.
美女  你叫什么
Hey, pretty girl. What's your name?
-莎拉  -莎拉
-Sarah. -oh, Sarah.
莎拉  名字很性感  你单身吗
Sarah. Sexy name. You single?
我受宠若惊  但我不喜欢女孩
Look, I'm flattered, but I'm not into girls.
不是的  我不是在给自己搭讪
Oh, oh, no, no, no. It's not for me.
是给他
It's for him.
他叫乔什  今年三十岁  帅气又土豪
His name is Josh, he's 30, sexy and super successful.
既然他那么好  你怎么不跟他约会
Oh. Well, if he's so great, why don't you date him?
因为他是我老板  那样太不专业了
Because he's my boss, and that would be super unprofessional.
-他笑起来确实挺可爱  -没错
- He does have a cute smile. - Yeah.
开保时捷的样子更可爱
Looks even cuter in his Porsche.
埃兰  冷静
Alan, calm down!
所以你变装皇后宾果的主持人不干了
So your Drag Queen Bingo host dropped out,
你需要另外找个男扮女装的人
And you need to find a man dressed as a woman.
不  我才不做
No, I will not do it.
我知道你叫我亚洲小公主
I know you call me your Asian Princess,
但那仅限在卧室
but that's just for the bedroom!
不许吃软糖蛋糕
Step away from the Fudgey Cakes!
我们会给你找到别的主持  我保证  再见
We will find you another bingo host, I promise. Bye!
我听见你说需要个主持
Did I hear you say you need a bingo host?
我在教堂主持过宾果  可棒了
Because I call bingo at church, and I'm damn good at it.
相信我  尤兰达  这活不适合你
Trust me, Yolanda. This is not the gig for you.
别这样嘛  我可会带气氛了
Oh, come on! I got a whole shtick.
摸出I8  我喊"我吃了[音似]一整个披萨"
I grab a ball and I call out, "I-8... a whole pizza, y'all."
牧师都被我气死了
It killed the reverend.
没关系  他去更好的地方了
It's okay, he's in a better place.
对不起  尤兰达  但真的不行
Sorry, Yolanda, but the answer's no.
别这样嘛  为什么我不行
Oh, come on. Why can't I do it?
因为你不是...
Because you're not a--
等等  你转一圈
You know what? Spin.
也许你确实行
You might be able to pull this off.
我就说嘛
That's what I've been saying!
谢谢  艾略特  你真棒
Thanks, Elliot, oh! You the man!
不  有"棒"的是你
No, you are.
别怕饿  午餐到
Never fear, lunch is here.
好啦  我们有叉子刀子勺子  和莎拉
Okay. We've got a fork, a knife, a spoon, and a Sarah.
莎拉是啥
What's a Sarah?
这个  她跟我住一栋楼
This. She lives in my building,
特别可爱  是个律师助理  还练普拉提
she's super cute, she's a paralegal, she does Pilates.
你这是干什么
What are you doing?
你知道你有阵子没约会了吧
So you know how you haven't dated anybody in a while?
我选择的  我来选  不是她们
By choice. My choice, not theirs.
-那我的选择是莎拉  -不用  谢谢
- Well, my choice is Sarah. - No, thank you.
加比  自己能找女朋友的  我是谁啊
Gabi, I can get a girl on my own. I'm me.
但这是对我最好的选择
But it would be the best thing for me--
还有你  莎拉  还有大家
you-- Sarah-- everyone.
我只是觉得我们之间发生那么多...
Look, I just feel like after everything that happened between us,
-你懂的  四以后  -加比  够惹
- you know, all that "sturff"... - Gabi, "enurf."
我只是觉得如果我跟别人约会了
I just thought you might be a little uncomfortable
而你没有  你会不舒服
if I'm dating someone and you're not
因为你也许还对某人有感觉呢
because you might still have feelings for a certain someone.
自恋狂
Set it up.
要不这样  我们一起出去吧
Better yet, why don't we all go out together.
怎么样  我和莎拉  你和动物
How about that? Me, Sarah, you, animal.
好啊
Great!
好的  但能今晚就去吗
Okay, oh, uh, but can we do it tonight?
因为今天是星期三
Because today is wednesday,
我编了个特别好笑的内衣笑话
and I made a really cute underwear joke.
加比告诉我你是乐队的鼓手
So Gabi tells me you are the drummer in a band.
-太帅了  -没错  只差一首主打歌
- That's awesome. - Yeah. We're one hit from making it big.
我们乐队的名字叫"只差一首主打歌"
That's the name of our band, "One Hit From Making It Big."
你听过他们的歌吗
Have you heard any of their music?
没有  但我听过他在桌上打节奏
No, but I heard him tapping on the table.
特别有天赋
He's very talented.
莎拉  来帮我做甜点吧
So, uh, Sarah, do you want to help me with dessert?
如果那是"我们去谈谈男人"的暗号  那当然
If that's code for "Let's talk about the boys," hell yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
加比说你们是在她家认识的  你住在附近吗
Gabi mentioned you met, uh, at her place. Do you live nearby?
-只有周二周四才是  -什么
- Only on Tuesdays and Thursdays. - What?
是  周一周三会有扫大街的
Yeah, well, Mondays and Wednesdays is street cleaning
而我觉得周末最好还是把车停在城外
and weekends I find it best to park outside the city.
因为...你住在  你的车里吗
Because... you live... in your car?
没错
Yup.
我重新调整了座椅  几乎能在车里躺下
I re-jiggered the seat so I almost have a full recline.
而且我的空气清新剂是椰林飘香味
And I got a Pina Colada air refresher,
所以就感觉自己在度假
so it's like I'm always on vacation.
真不错  请稍等
Sweet. Hey, give me a second.
泰勒是个流浪汉
Tyler is homeless.
-什么  -他其实有家啦
- What? - I shouldn't say he's homeless.
车就是他的家  就像只乌龟
His car is his home, like a turtle.
好吧  你是怎么知道的
Okay, where is this coming from?
他自己跟我说的  还很自豪
- He told me, proudly.
-那只乌龟亲口告诉我的  -我不相信
- I got it straight from the turtle's mouth. - I don't believe you.
洗手间在哪
Hey, where's the bathroom?
就在走廊尽头
Oh, it's just right down the hall.
有个洗手间真好
Oh, I love bathrooms,
要不还得花25美分才能上厕所
I don't need a quarter to get into.
对了  我能不能顺便把衬衫洗了
Hey, is it cool if I hand-wash my shirt in there?
算了吧  也不脏
Oh, you know what? I'm cool.
这还是不能说明他无家可归
Okay, that doesn't prove he's homeless.
我这么问  是因为我住在我的车里
Oh, the reason I'm asking is 'cause I live in my car.
好吧  能说明
Okay, that does.
快来看看我今晚主持宾果的新裙子
Hey, y'all. Check out my new dress for hosting bingo night.
能展露我的身材曲线
It's gonna show off all my curves.
副乳也展露得出来啊
And maybe a little sideboob too.
-不错  -才不是
- Nice. - Not really.
你没有浮夸点的衣服吗  是酒吧哎
Don't you have anything flashier? It's a bar!
带亮片的  能突出你宽阔性感的肩膀
Something sparkly, that accentuates your broad sexy shoulders
和你粗壮有型的腿
and your strong, shapely legs.
-是啊  又不是去教堂玩宾果  -就是嘛
- Yeah! This ain't church bingo. - Testify!
但是如果要露那么多  我还得去脱毛
But if I'm gonna be showing all that skin, I gotta go get waxed.
不用的
Don't bother.
-早安  乔什  -你好
- Morning Josh - Oh hey.
昨晚和泰勒过得如何
How'd your night go last night with Tyler?
你们采取安全措施了吗
Did you guys use protection?
你懂的  系安全带了吗
You know, seat belts?
你跟莎拉也开这种玩笑吗
Oh, are those the kind of jokes you use on Sarah?
你们昨晚怎么样
How'd that work out for ya?
我感觉我们似乎还会再见的
Something tells me I'm gonna see her again.
-早  -我说吧
- Morning. - Told ya.
莎拉  昨晚我过得很开心
Hi, Sarah. I had a great night with you last night.
-我也是  -等会儿打给你吗
- Me too. - Call ya later?
等不及了
Can't wait.
加比  谢谢你把他介绍给我
Gabi, thanks for the awesome setup.
现在我放心多了  这城里奇葩太多
I'm just so relieved. There are so many weirdos in this city.
是啊  每条街上都有
Yep, there's one parked on every corner.
我可能把钥匙落在楼上了
I think I left my keys upstairs.
莎拉  我找到了你的...
Sarah, I found your...
一罐牙吗
jar of teeth?
好诡异  好诡异的一罐牙
Really, really creepy jar of teeth!
你妹啊
What the hell?
我肯定把钥匙放在这儿了
I know I must have put them up here somewhere.
你或许该看看在不在包里
Uh, maybe you wanna... check your purse?
我看看...
Let's see...
在这儿呢
here they are. Ah!
明明在眼前
Don't you hate it when something
却看不见  真是太烦人了
is right in front of you and you can't see it?
我什么都没看见
No, I didn't see anything.
好  家里见啦
Okay, well, see you back at the apartment.
我锁了门就见不着你了
Not if I lock my door.
乔什  乔什
Josh, Josh, Josh, Josh!
我一不小心把莎拉的包弄掉了
I accidentally knocked Sarah's purse over,
你永远也不会相信我看到了什么
and you're never gonna believe what came out!
-一罐牙  -什么
- A jar of teeth. - What?
一罐牙  还不止呢
A jar of teeth! But wait, that's not all.
还有个银色的尖东西  拔牙的东西
There was also a silver pointy thing, and a pully thing,
还有个钳牙的东西
and a clampy thing,
我觉得那都不是好东西
and I think she uses them for bad things.
加比  淡定  我不知道你看见的...
Okay, Gabi, calm down. I'm not sure what you saw...
没错  还有个锯子
There was a saw too!
你不能再约她了
You have to stop dating her.
加比  我明白了
Oh, Gabi, I see what's going on here.
你还记得你以为你在约会
Remember when you thought I'd be uncomfortable
而我会不高兴吗
if you were dating somebody and I wasn't?
不
No.
不  不是这样的好吗
No. That is not what's happening here, okay?
她是变态  可能很危险
She's sick. She could be dangerous.
我没说你是故意这样的
Look, I'm not saying you're doing it on purpose.
只是觉得你可能还没发现
I just think it's a little unconscious.
是吗  我觉得你最后会在笼子里喊"救命"
Yeah? Well, I think you're gonna be in a cage yelling, "Help me!"
但因为没了牙  只能喊出来"巨闷"
But because you have no teeth, it's gonna come out, "Melp me!
"巨闷"
"Melp me!
Melp me!"
我把她包碰掉到地上  开始还想
I dropped her purse on the ground, and at first I was like,
"不好  别把她手机摔坏了"
"Oh, no, I hope I didn't break her phone."
然后就是  "不好  我找到一罐牙齿"
And then I was like, "Oh, no, I found a jar of teeth!"
真的吗  加比
Really, Gabi?
还是这也像当初
Or is this like the time
你觉得那匹巡逻马对你抛媚眼那样
you thought that police horse winked at you?
不是的  我亲眼看见了  还拿在手里
No! Okay? I saw them. I held them in my hands.
要怎么才能让别人相信我
What is it gonna take to get people to believe me?
-你不用向我证明的  -没错
- You don't have to prove it to me. - Yes, yes!
-我要证明  -我不会帮...
- I have to prove it. - I'm not gonna help--
你还要帮我
And you're gonna help me!
莎拉  能帮我个忙吗  我的狗狗丢了
Sarah, hi. Can you help me? I lost my dog.
你养狗吗  我以为他们不给住户养狗
You have a dog? I didn't think they let us have pets.
没错  这狗是朋友的
Right. Uh... it's a friend's dog...
瑞恩·高斯林
Ryan Gosling.
你和瑞恩·高斯林是朋友吗
You're friends with Ryan Gosling?
不不  是狗叫这名字
No, no. No, that's the name of the dog.
我好像看见他了  你能帮我下吗
I think I just saw him! Um, can you please come help?
-瑞恩·高斯林  来  宝贝  -高司令
- Ryan Gosling! Come here, boy! - Ryan!
好  如果我是罐牙齿  我会在哪
Okay. If I were a creepy jar of teeth, where would I be?
高司令  高司令
Ryan Gosling! Ryan Gosling!
不对  是薄荷糖
Oh, no, these are Tic-Tacs.
抱歉  祝你能找到高司令
I'm sorry, good luck finding Ryan Gosling.
辛迪  凯琳  大卫  麦克  安迪  乔什
乔什  天啊
Josh-- oh, my god.
我好害怕  我好害怕
I'm so scared. I'm so scared.
你好  我看到了你在网上的广告
Hi, I'm calling you about your ad on Craigslist.
你的电锯还在吗
Do you still have the electric saw?
很好  它能锯断骨头吗
Oh, good. Does it cut through bone?
太好了  谢谢
Perfect. Thank you.
一定要是索菲亚  一定要是索菲亚
Please be Sofia. Please be Sofia. Please be...
我收到你短信  就开车来了
I got your text and I jumped in my car.
又收到了你的照片  忘了怎么开车
Then I got your photo and forgot how to drive.
不如来杯红酒吧
How does a glass of wine sound?
你想给他下毒  偷他牙齿
Like you're gonna poison him and steal his teeth!
-没问题  -所以我都倒好了
- Sounds good to me. - That's why I already poured one.
真的吗
Really?
那是毒药  别喝  别喝
It's poison! Don't drink it! Don't drink it, no!
别喝  别喝  不
Don't drink it! Don't drink it! No!
-离他远点  你个变态  -加比
- Get away from him, you freak! - Gabi!
你在我家里干什么
What the hell are you doing in my apartment?
-你解释啊  -你才要解释
- Explain yourself! - Explain yourself!
是你躲在我的柜子里
You're the one hiding in my closet.
是你有一柜子的牙
You're the one with a closet full of teeth!
乔什  你看  记得你还说我疯了吗
Josh, look! Do you remember when you thought I was crazy?
-莎拉  -我能解释
- Uh, Sarah? - I can explain.
我用牙齿做首饰  在网上卖
I make jewelry out of teeth and sell it on Etsy.
是啊  说得像真的一样
Yeah, like that's a thing.
就是真的
It is a thing.
那为什么罐子上都是名字  莎拉
Well, why are there all the names on the jars, Sarah?
那是我客户的名字
They're my customers.
乔什可不是你客户  你解释啊
Well, Josh is not a customer. So, explain that.
我想做对袖扣  给他个惊喜
I was making him a surprise pair of cufflinks.
听见没  加比  她想给我个惊喜...
You hear that, Gabi? She was making me a surprise pair of...
送牙齿袖扣吗
teeth cufflinks.
莎拉  你的故事还有个小漏洞
Well, Sarah, there's just one little hole in your story.
一个小蛀牙
A cavity, if you will.
你说的这些
Where is all of this so-called
牙齿首饰我怎么没见着
teeth jewelry I am hearing so much about?
故事是真的
Story checks out.
谜题解开了
Mystery explained.
任务完成  我走了
My work here is done. I will take my leave.
再见
Goodbye!
-真对不起  -不是你的错
- I'm so sorry. - It's not your fault.
很多人都觉得牙齿首饰奇怪
A lot of people think teeth jewelry's weird.
谢天谢地
Okay, thank god.
我没敢说  不过真的有点奇怪
I wasn't gonna say anything, but it's kinda weird.
我自己根本不戴
I mean, I don't even wear it myself.
但想买的人很多
But there is a whole market for it:
-哥特  电摇迷  口腔治疗师  -真的吗
- Goths, metalheads, dental hygienists. - Really?
我觉得这还挺酷的
I guess that's kinda cool.
你的牙都是从哪来的
Where do you get these teeth from?
我闯进停尸房拔的
I break into morgues.
她闯进...  我该走了
She breaks into-- yep, time to go.
谢谢
Thank you!
真漂亮  姑娘
Damn! Work it, girl!
谢谢  亲爱的
Thank you, baby!
有资本就炫出来
If you got it, flaunt it!
尤兰达  你看着就像个皇后
Yolanda, you look like a queen.
欢迎来到  变装皇后宾果
"变装皇后宾果"吗
Drag queen bingo?
女士们先生们  和我一起掌声欢迎
Ladies and gentlemen, help me welcome to the stage
大家眼中的珍宝[喉结]  尤兰达小姐
The Adam's apple of everyone's eye, Miss Yolanda!
想都别想
Oh, hell no!
等等  尤兰达
Wait, Yolanda.
你想让我去抓球吗
You want me to pull balls?
我第一个要抓掉的  就是你的"球"
The first balls I'm gonna pull are yours!
-尤兰达  -听听他们  尤兰达
- Yolanda! - Listen to them, Yolanda.
大家都喜欢你
They love you.
尤兰达  尤兰达
Yolanda! Yolanda!
他们都在喊我名字
Well, they are chanting my name.
那现在  派对开始吧
So let's get this party started.
跟着我喊起来
Let me hear you say "hey!"
今晚的第一个球是
The first ball of the night is...
B18
B-18.
如果想泡我  最好满十八哦
If you want a piece of this, you better be 18!
-停尸房拔的吗  -停尸房
- Morgues? - Morgues.
老天  我们也是懂了
Man, we sure can pick 'em.
-我们吗  -好吧  就我
- We? - Okay, fine. Me.
你看...
Look...
加比  你知道我们不会
Gabi, you know we're not always gonna be
总是同时有对象的
dating people at the same exact time.
我知道  我只是想让我们回到正常
Yeah, I know. I think I was just trying to get us back to normal.
-你懂的  在那些...  -"四情"之前吗
- You know, before all of that... - "Sturff"?
对  那些四
Yeah, "Sturff."
有时候就会发生这些四
Well, look, sometimes "sturff" happens.
我们要试着忘掉
And we gotta get past that.
你知道我们之间是什么样吗
And you know what we have going for us?
从你为我工作开始
Ever since you started working for me,
我们的关系就从没正常过
our relationship's been anything but normal.
对我们来说  奇怪才是正常
So for us, normal is weird.
而正常才奇怪
And weird is normal.
现在开始  我们接受这奇怪就好
From now on, I think we should just embrace the weird.
奇怪是我们要接受的
The weird is what we need to embrace.
-停尸房拔的  -停尸房
- Morgues! - Morgues!
好了  明天见  怪物
All right. See ya tomorrow, weirdo.
再见  奇葩
Okay, bye, freak show.
-你好  伙计  -要接受奇怪
- 'Sup, bro? - Embracing the weird.
-你好  泰勒  -你好
- Hey, Tyler. - Hey, you.
今天是周四  我把车停楼下
It's Thursday, so I was parked downstairs
一整天脑子里都在想着你
and I just couldn't get your pretty little face
漂亮的小脸蛋
out of my head all day,
所以就想上楼来见见本尊
So I thought I'd come up and see it in person.
-你是想上厕所  对不对  -憋死我了
- You have to use the bathroom, don't you? - So bad.
你家还有那松饼吗
Hey, do you have any more of those muffins?
要接受奇怪
Embrace the weird.
我本该生你的气
I should be mad at you,
但我得承认
but I gotta admit it,
那还挺好玩
that was fun.
你的确没料到  但像个男人一样挺住了
It was a big surprise, but you took it like a man.
没错  你在台上真棒
You sure did. You were amazing out there.
是吗
I was?
谢谢
Thank you.
我能请你喝杯酒吗
Can I buy you a drink?
请我喝两杯好了
You can buy me two.
先说清楚
So I'm clear,
这家伙以为我是男人才来搭讪的  对吗
this guy's flirting with me because he thinks I'm a man, right?
宾果
Bingo.
你好  我叫弗兰克
Hi, I'm Frank.